<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sangeeta Menon</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sangeeta Menon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Execute Python Code</title>
      <link>/tech_writing/execute_python_code/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tech_writing/execute_python_code/</guid>
      <description>Overview Steps - Script Mode Steps - Interactive Mode   Overview The following tutorial is for absolute beginners trying to learn how to execute Python code in a reasonably modern Ubuntu Linux environment. It assumes that you have Python 3 installed in your machine (if not, execute sudo apt-get install python3 from the terminal). Also, you should know your way around the Ubuntu desktop interface - the bare minimum necessary for finding and launching applications like Terminal, Gedit, or VS Code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impact of COVID-19 on the IT Industry</title>
      <link>/personal_blog/covid_impact_it_industry/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/personal_blog/covid_impact_it_industry/</guid>
      <description>Corona. Covid-19. The very word invokes fear in the mind and prayer on the lips. When the first case was detected in China no one had an inkling about its global consequences.
In fact, the news was probably taken with a pinch of salt. It is when the cases spiked across the globe that the entire situation spiralled out of control. Given the lethality of the virus, the fear was palpable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awful Writer or “Awe”full Writer</title>
      <link>/tech_writing/awful_writer_or_aweful_writer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tech_writing/awful_writer_or_aweful_writer/</guid>
      <description>Before you read If you are reading this article, I assume that the majority of you must be technical writers. The peer-review checklist might be firmly etched in your mind. Please make sure this checklist in disabled. If doing so is not possible, just click the X sign at the top-right corner of the screen. Also, if you have no sense of humor, it is mandatory to click the X sign.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ensure That vs Ensure</title>
      <link>/tech_writing/ensure_that_vs_ensure/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tech_writing/ensure_that_vs_ensure/</guid>
      <description>“That” is the question! Examples References   “That” is the question! A prominent dilemma among writers is whether to use “ensure that”, or simply “ensure”. There is no consensus in the community about the inclusion of “that”, but the following discussion might shed some light.
 Examples Consider the following sentences:
 Before installation, ensure that the md5 signature matches with the original package.
 Silly example does not ensure clarity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transcend Beyond Lay-offs</title>
      <link>/personal_blog/transcend_beyond_layoffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/personal_blog/transcend_beyond_layoffs/</guid>
      <description>Post coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>